Federal Art Project, Photographic Division
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Artist Files, circa 1920-1965, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-24; 9.6 linear feet)
  - Crimi, Alfred D., circa 1941, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 16)
    includes possible photo of Crimi
  - Crimi, Charles, 1937-1939, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Criss, Francis, 1936-1941, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 18)
    includes photo of Criss, October 1930
  - Cronbach, Robert M., circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Cross, Louise, circa 1936-circa 1941, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Crow, Claude, 1939-1941, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Csoka, Stephen, 1941, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Cunning, John, 1936, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 23)
  - D'Agostino, Vincent, 1940-1941, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Dames, Chester, circa 1940, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Daniel, Lewis C., 1940, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Daniels, Jacob F., 1940, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Darnell, Janet, 1941, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Datz, A. Mark, 1938, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Davey, Randall, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Davidson, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Davis, C. W., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Davis, Charles, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Davis, Hubert, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Davis, Lew E., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Davis, Richard, circa 1936, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Davis, Stuart, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 37)
    includes photo of Davis, January 1939
  - Davis, Wyatt, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 38)
  - Dawson, Omer G., circa 1945, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 39)
  - Day, Selma, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R: 1163) (Box 5 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Dean, Bob, 1938, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Dearing, Elizabeth, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 2)
    includes photos of Dearing, circa 1939
  - De Brennecke, Nina, circa 1938, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 3)
  - De Cordoba, Mathilde, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 4)
  - De Felipe, Juan, 1937, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Dehn, Adolf, circa 1940, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 6)
    includes photos of Adolf and Virginia Dehn, Reginald Marsh and Elizabeth Olds
  - De La Guadagne, Armand, circa 1936-circa 1937, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Delgado, Eduardo, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Delman, Elias Ben, 1940-1941, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 9)
  - De Lorenzo, Fred, 1941, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 10)
  - De Martini, Joseph, circa 1939-circa 1941, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 11)
  - De Rivera, Jose, circa 1937, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 12)
    includes photos of De Rivera
  - De Rocco, Jovan, 1937-1939, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Derup, Karl, circa 1941, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 14)
  - De Vault, David S., 1940, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 15)
  - De Vegh, G., circa 1935-circa 1937, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 16)
  - Diener, Irving, circa 1939, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Dill, Elaine, 1938, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 18)
  - Di Nicola, Joseph, circa 1935-circa 1938, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Dirk, Nathaniel, 1937, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 20)
    photo of Dirk, 1937 October
  - Di Tore, Salvatore, circa 1938, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Dodd, Lamar, circa 1939, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Doi, Isami, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 23)
  - Doktor, Raphael, 1940, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Donaldson, Alice Willits, 1938-1940, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Donskoy-Kallman, I., 1939, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Downer, Kenneth, circa 1937-circa 1940, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Drake, Venetia, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Dreis, Edward, circa 1938, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Drewes, Werner, 1941, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Driggs, Elsie, 1938, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Du Bois, Guy Pène, 1940, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Duhmart, G., 1939, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Dunham, Francis, 1936-1938, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Dunstan, W. H., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Durant, Helen, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Dwight, Mabel, circa 1938-circa 1940, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 37)
  - Eaton, Dorothy, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 38)
  - Eby, Kerr, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 39)
  - Edie, Stuart Carson, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Egri, Ruth, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 41)
    includes photos of Egri, 1937 April
  - Egri, Theodore, circa 1938-circa 1939, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 42)
  - Ehlreich, Edward, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 43)
  - Eichenberg, Fritz, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 44)
  - Eilshemius, Louis, 1941, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 45)
  - Elliot, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1163) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 46)
  - Emanuel, Herzl, circa 1937-circa 1940, (R: 1163-1164) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 47)
  - Emergen, Fred, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1164) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 48)
  - Emerson, C., 1938, (R: 1164) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 49)
  - Emerson, Sybil, 1937-1941, (R: 1164) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 50)
  - Emery, Irene, circa 1937, (R: 1164) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 51)
    photo of Emery, circa 1937
  - Engers, Leon, 1937, (R: 1164) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 52)
  - Ennis, George Pearse, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1164) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 53)
    includes photos of Ennis, circa 1936
  - Ensel, Henry, 1937-1941, (R: 1164) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 54)
  - Enters, Angna, 1940, (R: 1164) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 55)
    photo of Enters
  - Esman, Betty, 1937-1938, (R: 1164) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 56)
  - Etellback, A., 1941, (R: 1164) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 57)
  - Etting, Emlen, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1164) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 58)
  - Euffa, Ray, 1940, (R: 1164) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 59)
  - Everett, Roberta, 1941, (R: 1164) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 60)
  - Evergood, Philip, circa 1936-circa 1940, (R: 1164) (Box 6 (hol), Folder 61)
    includes photos of Evergood, 1938 May, 1939 June
  - Faber, Arthur, circa 1937-circa 1940, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Faber, J. W., 1936, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Fabry, Alois, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 3)
  - Fastovsky, Isaac, 1937-1938, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Fay, Hans, 1939, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Faye, Harold, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Federici, Gaetano, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Feinstein, David, 1940, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Ferrara, Vincent, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Ferrugio, Remo, circa 1936-circa 1941, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Ferstadt, Louis, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 11)
    includes photos of Ferstadt
  - Ficini, Gino, circa 1938, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Fidaroff, Simon, 1937, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Fields, Earl Thomas, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 14)
  - Fields, Mitchell, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Filmus, Tully, circa 1937-circa 1942, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 16)
  - Filtzer, Hyman, circa 1937-circa 1942, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Finta, Alexander, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 18)
    includes photos of Finta, 1939 June
  - Fiorillo, Anthony, 1938-1939, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Flannery, Vaughn, 1940, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Fleishman, Gertrude, circa 1937, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Fleri, Joseph C., circa 1936-circa 1941, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Flint, Alice, 1941, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 23)
  - Flint, Leroy, 1937, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Floegel, Alfred E., 1939-1941, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Floherty, John J., circa 1945, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Fogel, Seymour, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 27)
    includes photos of Fogel
  - Folinsbee, John Fulton, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Forbes, Donald, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Fortess, Karl Eugene, circa 1938, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Fossum, Sydney Glen, 1940, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Frank, Bena Virginia, circa 1941, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Frankel, Josephine, circa 1936-circa 1941, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Frankel, Max, 1938-1942, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Franklin, George, 1937, (R: 1164) (Box 7 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Freeman, Don, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Freilicher, Hy, circa 1941, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Frelinghuysen, Thomas T. K., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 3)
  - French, Jared, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Friedman, Arnold, 1938, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Friedman, Mark, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Friedman, Sidney, 1939-1940, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Frisch, Sari, 1937-1938, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Fuller, Robert, circa 1937, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Furedi, Lily, 1937-1939, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Furness, Richard, circa 1936, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Gaige, Richard, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Gallagher, Michael J., circa 1937, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Galos, Ben, circa 1940-circa 1941, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 14)
  - Ganso, Emil, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Gantman, Edna, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 16)
  - Garcia, Estella, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Garrison, Robert, circa 1938-circa 1939, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 18)
    includes photo of Garrison, 1939 May
  - Gasparo, Oronzo, 1938, 1941, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Gassner, Mordi, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Gaulois, Helen, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 21)
    includes photos of Gaulois, 1938
  - Gelb, Donald, 1941, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Gelfand, Sydney, 1937, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 23)
  - Gellert, Hugo, 1939, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Gelman, Aaron, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Gentle, Robert, 1941, (R: 1164) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Gerbino, Rosario, 1940, (R: 1165) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Gerchik, Paul, 1939, (R: 1165) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Gershoy, Eugene, circa 1937-circa 1940, (R: 1165) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 29)
    includes photos of Gershoy, 1938, 1940
  - Gikow, Ruth, circa 1938-circa 1940, (R: 1165) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Gildersleeve, Jack B., circa 1945, (R: 1165) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Gilien, Theodore, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Girolami, George, circa 1936-circa 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Girouard, Gerard, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Glenn, John S., circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 35)
    includes photos of Glenn, circa 1937
  - Glicenstein, Enrico, circa 1936-circa 1940, (R: 1165) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 36)
    includes photos of Glicenstein, 1940
  - Glickman, Maurice, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 37)
  - Glinsky, Vincent, circa 1939-circa 1942, (R: 1165) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 38)
    includes photos of Glinsky
  - Glintenkamp, H., 1940, (R: 1165) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 39)
  - Godwin, Earl, 1936-1939, (R: 1165) (Box 8 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Goeller, Charles Louis, 1938, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Goetz, Esther Becker, 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Goldat, Isaac, 1936-1937, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 3)
  - Good, Minnetta, 1938-1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Goodelman, Aaron J., circa 1936-circa 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Goodman, Bertram, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 6)
    includes photo of Goodman
  - Goodman, Job, circa 1938-circa 1939, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Goodrich, Gertrude, 1938-1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Goolst, Morris, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Gordin, Sid, 1936, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Gordon, Benjamin, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Gorelick, Boris, circa 1937-circa 1940, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Gorky, Arshile, circa 1935-circa 1936, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 13)
    includes photos of Gorky
  - Gotcliffe, Sidney, circa 1939-circa 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 14)
  - Gottlieb, Adolph, 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Gottlieb, Harry, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 16)
  - Gough, W., 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Graham, F. Wynn, 1937-1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 18)
  - Graham, Mies, 1939, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 19)
    photo of Mies
  - Grambs, Blanche, circa 1937-circa 1938, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Grant, Gordon, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Green, Russell, 1938, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Green, Wallace, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 23)
  - Greenbaum, James, 1939-1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Greene, Balcomb, 1937-1939, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 25)
    includes photo probably of Greene
  - Greene, G. Peter, 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Greene, H., 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Greenwood, Grace see: Ames, Grace Greenwood (Box 9 (hol))
  - Greenwood, Marion, 1936-1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 28)
    includes photos of Greenwood, 1936, 1940
  - Gregory, John, 1936, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Gregory, Peter, 1937-1938, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Gregory, Waylande, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 31)
    includes photo of Gregory
  - Griffith, Herbert, 1939, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Grippe, Peter, 1940-1942, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Gropper, William, 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Gross, Chaim, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Grossman, Isidore, 1940-1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Groth, John, 1940-1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 37)
  - Grunvald, Samuel, circa 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 38)
  - Gubin, Selma, circa 1936-circa 1940, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 39)
  - Guck, Edna, circa 1935-circa 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Guerruiriprbe, Trude, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 41)
  - Guglielmi, O. Louis, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 42)
  - Gunn, Arthur, 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 43)
  - Guston, Philip, circa 1939-circa 1940, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 44)
    includes photos of Guston
  - Guteman, Ernest, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 45)
  - Gutieri, Ralph, 1938, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 46)
  - Guy, James, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 9 (hol), Folder 47)
  - Hague, Raoul, circa 1935-circa 1939, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Halfant, Jules, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Hammer, Amelia, 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 3)
  - Hancke, F., 1941-1942, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Hannah, Muriel, circa 1937-circa 1940, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Harari, Hananiah, 1938, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Hardy, Howard, 1940, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Harkavy, Minna R., circa 1936, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Harlin, 1938, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Harmon, Lily, 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Harnly, Perkins, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Harrington, Mabel, 1936-1937, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Harris, Louis, 1937-1938, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Harriton, Abraham, circa 1938-circa 1942, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 14)
    includes photos of Harriton, 1938
  - Hart, Agnes, 1939-1941, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Hartman, Bertram, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 16)
  - Hartman, M., 1941, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Hartman, Rosella, 1938, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 18)
  - Hartman, Samuel, 1940, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Haseltine, Herbert, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 20)
  - Haucke, Frederick, 1939, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 21)
  - Haupt, Theodore Gilbert, 1938-1942, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Hauser, Alonzo, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1165) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 23)
  - Hayes, Vertis, circa 1937, (R: 1166) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Hebald, Milton Elting, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1166) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 25)
  - Hecht, Zoltan, circa 1937-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 26)
  - Heckman, Albert William, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Heino, Virka & Otto, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Heinrich, Christian, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Heins, John, circa 1936, (R: 1166) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Helfond, Riva, 1940-1941, (R: 1166) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Heller, Helen West, circa 1936-circa 1940, (R: 1166) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 32)
    includes photos of Heller, 1936
  - Henkel, August, circa 1939, (R: 1166) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 33)
    includes photos of Henkel
  - Henn, Rudolph, 1937-1942, (R: 1166) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Henning, Charles, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1166) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Henoch, Hanley, circa 1937, (R: 1166) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Henricksen, Ralph, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1166) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 37)
    includes photo of Henricksen, 1938
  - Henry, Charles T., 1939-1941, (R: 1166) (Box 10 (hol), Folder 38)
  - Hermes, Allen, 1937-1939, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Hershman, Edna, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 2)
    includes photos of Hershman, circa 1939
  - Heum, Rudolph, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 3)
  - Hicks, 1941, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 4)
  - Higgins, Victor, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Hiler, Hilaire, 1940, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Hirsch, Willard, circa 1939-circa 1941, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 7)
    includes photos of Hirsch, circa 1939
  - Hoff, Guy, circa 1940, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Hoffbauer, Charles, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Hoffman, Ben, 1938, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Hoffman, Seth, 1937-1938, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Hoglander, H., circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Holmberg, Lawrence, 1937, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 13)
  - Holmes, Henry, 1937-1938, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 14)
  - Holmes, Stuart, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 15)
  - Holston, Edith, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 16)
  - Holzhauer, Emil, 1939, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 17)
  - Hondius, Gerrit, 1937-1941, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 18)
  - Hood, Richard, circa 1936, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 19)
  - Hord, Donal, circa 1937, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 20)
    includes photos of Hord with others including Arthur Ames, Holger Cahill, Homer Dana, Joseph Daynish, Thyris Field, Pat Fleming, Jean Goodwin, Nelson Partridge, and Stanton MacDonald Wright
  - Horn, Milton, circa 1934-circa 1939, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 21)
    includes photos of Horn, circa 1937
  - Horowitz, Jacques, circa 1937, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 22)
  - Horr, Axel, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 23)
    includes photos of Horr, 1937, 1940
  - Hovannes, John, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 24)
  - Hovell, Joseph, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 25)
    includes photo of Hovell, January 1936
  - Hover, T. A., 1940, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 26)
  - How, Kenneth, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 27)
  - Hullenkremer, Oden, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 28)
  - Hulme, James Sanford, 1937-1939, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 29)
  - Hunt, Georgine, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 30)
  - Hunt, Thomas, 1937-1941, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 31)
  - Hutchinson, Mary, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 32)
  - Hyun, Paul, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 33)
  - Imler, Edgar, 1936-1938, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 34)
  - Ingersoll, G., 1937, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 35)
  - Irwin, Howard Lee, circa 1937-circa 1939, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 36)
  - Ishigaki, Eitaro, circa 1937-circa 1940, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 37)
    includes photos of Ishigaki
  - Jack, Mable, 1939, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 38)
  - Jacobi, Eli, circa 1936-circa 1939, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 39)
  - Jacobs, Deyo, circa 1940, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 40)
  - Jacobson, Emanuel, circa 1936, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 41)
  - Jacoby, Samuel, 1938-1941, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 42)
  - Janni, Pino, 1937, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 43)
  - Janowsky, Bela, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 44)
  - Jansen, Richard, circa 1938, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 45)
    photo of Jansen
  - Jefferson, Louise E., 1938, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 46)
  - Jenkins, Leonard Seweryn, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 47)
    includes photos of Jenkins, 1937
  - Johnson, Thomas Loftin, circa 1936-circa 1938, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 48)
    includes photos of Johnson, circa 1938
  - Jones, Joe, circa 1943, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 49)
    includes photo of Jones
  - Jones, Leon Foster, 1938, (R: 1166) (Box 11 (hol), Folder 50)
  - Jonson, Raymond, circa 1935-circa 1942, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 1)
  - Julius, Oscar H., 1939-1942, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 2)
  - Jurls, A., 1941, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 3)
  - Juszko, Jeno, circa 1937-circa 1941, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 4)
    includes photos of Juszko, circa 1939
  - Kachinsky, Alexander, 1938, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 5)
  - Kadulin, Vladimir, 1940-1941, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 6)
  - Kagy, Sheffield, 1937, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 7)
  - Kainen, Jacob, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 8)
  - Kallem, Herbert, 1940-1941, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 9)
  - Kallem, Henry, circa 1938-circa 1941, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 10)
  - Kaminsky, Dora, 1938, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 11)
  - Kamrowski, Gerome, 1941, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 12)
  - Kantor, Israel, 1937-1941, (R: 1166) (Box 12 (hol), Folder 13)